bestgadgetry.com 2010-05-28

# Privacy Policy | BestGadgetry.com

#### You're currently on:

**_Privacy Policy_**

This privacy policy applies only to **www.bestgadgetry.com**  
BestGadgetry.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Under the Data Protection Act 1998, BestGadgetry.com has a legal duty to protect any personal information it collects from you.

**What information do we collect about you?**  
BestGadgetry.com does not capture and store any personal information about an individual who accesses this website, except where he or she voluntarily chooses to give Best Gadgetry personal information via email, or by using an electronic form on the website.

**How will we use the information about you?**  
>We will collect information about you to process your order, manage your account and, if you agree, to email you about other products and services we think may be of interest to you.  
>We use your information collected from the website to personalise your repeat visits to our website.   
>BestGadgetry.com may also use aggregate information and statistics for the purposes of monitoring website usage in order to help us develop the website and our services and may provide such aggregate information to third parties. These statistics will not include information that can be used to identify any individual.  
>Best Gadgetry will only hold your information for as long as necessary for the purpose for which it was collected. BestGadgetry.com will not sell, distribute or disclose information about you or your personal usage of the website without your express consent or unless required to do so by law. If you subscribe to our mailing lists for new release and other information, we may also ask you to answer various general questions about yourself. You might be asked to specify the areas in which you are interested in so that we can tailor the information which we sent to you to cover the topics and merchandise we believe you might be interested in. By subscribing to our mailing lists, you accept that your personal data may be used for such purposes.  
>Please note that we do provide links to other sites, which may not be governed by this Privacy Policy. BestGadgetry.com is not responsible for the data protection and privacy practices within any of these other sites. We encourage you to be aware of this when you leave our site and to read the data protection and privacy statements on other websites you visit which collect your personal information.  
>BestGadgetry.com uses cookies on its site. A cookie is a text file that identifies your computer to Best Gadgetry server. Cookies collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information. This information is used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity. Cookies in themselves do not identify the individual user, just the computer used. Cookies are not used to collect any personal information.  
> You have the opportunity to set your computer to accept all cookies, to notify you when a cookie is issued, or not to receive cookies at any time. The way in which you do this depends upon the web browser which you use. Please refer to the "Help" function for your browser. If you accept cookies, they may remain on your computer for many years, unless you delete them. Please note that turning off cookies may limit your use of our website and website services.  
>Best Gadgetry may also use the information we gather to notify you about important changes and alterations to the website, or offers of products, services or information that might be of particular interest to you. Your information may also be transferred to another company (based in the European Union or in a country ensuring an adequate level of protection) in the event of a sale of our company to a third party. In that event we will endeavour to ensure that your rights in respect of the processing of personal data are adequately and appropriately protected.  
>In processing your order, we may send your details to, and also use information from credit reference agencies and fraud prevention agencies.  
>All the personal information collected via this website is recorded in a secure database.  
>All Best Gadgetry employees and data processors, who have access to or are associated with the processing of personal information, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of that information.  
>Best Gadgetry ensures that your personal data will not be disclosed to government institutions and authorities except if required or allowed by law.  
>Please note that unless encrypted, email messages sent via the internet may not be secure and could be intercepted and read by someone else. Please bear this in mind when deciding whether to include personal or sensitive information in any email messages you intend to send.  
>By submitting your information and ticking the requisite boxes on any order form or when subscribing to the services available on our website, you expressly consent to such use and transfer of that information to the extent permitted by applicable law. If Best Gadgetry changes this privacy policy it will post the changes on this page. Continued use of the service will signify that you agree to any such changes. If at any time you wish to stop receiving our newsletter or any other information you may have requested from us or any other company, please email or write to the address below or click the Unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email you receive from us.  
**Users 16 and under**  
If you are aged 16 or under, please get your parent/guardian's permission before hand whenever you provide personal information to Best Gadgetry website. Users without this consent are not allowed to provide us with personal information.

**Data Protection**  
BestGadgetry.com will process any personal information that it collects in accordance with the [Data Protection Act 1998](http://www.opsi.gov.uk/Acts/Acts1998/ukpga_19980029_en_1). If you wish to access personal information collected from you via this website or if you have an enquiry or concern regarding the processing of personal data by Best Gadgetry, please contact: [customerservices@bestgadgetry.com](mailto:customerservices@bestgadgetry.com)

Under the Data Protection Act 1998, you have a right to request a copy of the information we hold about you. BestGadgetry.com will provide you with a legible copy of the personal information it holds and to which you are entitled upon request. This will be sent to you within 30 days of your request - although Best Gadgetry almost always requires proof of your identity before supplying the information (in order to mitigate the risk of supplying information to the wrong person) and may ask you for further information to assist in locating your personal information. You may have to pay a small charge before the information is supplied.  
We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate.

**Changes to our privacy policy**  
We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this webpage. You may wish to check this webpage every time you submit personal information to the website. This privacy policy was last updated on 27.10.09

**How to contact us**  
Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you:  
By email: [customerservices@bestgadgetry.com](mailto:customerservices@bestgadgetry.com)
